<c>
<b>
ROSSIYSKAYA FEDERATSIYA
<b>
*   *   *
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT
of the Russian Federation
hereby presents
<b>
#P
#u
#s
<b>
with the
<b>
MEDAL NESTEROVA
( #m )
<b>
<b>
<l>
For distinguishing himself by meritorious achievement while participating in sustained aerial flight in support of active military operations. During these flights, he displayed the highest order of air discipline and acted in accordance with the best traditions of the military service.
<b>
<b>
<r>
On #d,  .