<c>
ROSSIYSKAYA FEDERATSIYA
<b>
*   *    ((*))    *   *
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT
of the Russian Federation
takes pride in presenting the
<b>
MEDAL ORDENA
"ZA ZASLUGI PERED OTETSESTVOM"
I Stepeni s Mechami
( #m
to the Fatherland, with Swords )
<b>
to
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
As an excellent officer, and an ace pilot of note, #p has displayed incomparable and daring airmanship to successfully complete his assigned missions, himself engaging the enemy in many victorious contests. Through his gallantry and his devotion to duty, he demonstrates the highest values of a Russian patriot, and renders service of the greatest distinction to the Federation.
<b>
<b>
<r>
Moskva, #d  .