<c>
<b>
ROSSIYSKAYA FEDERATSIYA
<b>
*   *   *
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT
of the Russian Federation
hereby presents
<b>
#P
#u
#s
<b>
with the
<b>
MEDAL "ZA OTVAGU"
( #m )
<b>
<b>
<l>
For exemplary valor in active operations. While engaged in uneven aerial combat over #t, on #d, #p displayed superior airmanship skills and abnegation to successfully complete his assigned mission, inflicting heavy damage upon the enemy.