<c>
ROSSIYSKAYA FEDERATSIYA
<b>
*   *    ((*))    *   *
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT
of the Russian Federation
has exceptionally
Approved and Ordered that the
<b>
ORDEN SV. GEORGIYA IV Step.
( #m )
<b>
shall be Conferred on
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
On #d, #p, renowned already as a Hero of the Russian Federation and a Full Cavalier of St. George, fearlessly engaged a hostile force over #t, facing extremely determined opposition and overwhelming odds, yet could inflict crippling damage upon the enemy. This Cross will testify to Russia's eternal respect for the great military feats achieved by #p.