<c>
ROSSIYSKAYA FEDERATSIYA
<b>
*   *    ((*))    *   *
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT
of the Russian Federation
takes pride in Conferring the
<b>
ORDEN "ZA VOENNYE ZASLUGI"
( #m )
<b>
on
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
For exceptionally meritorious and distinguished service as a deputy squadron CO within the #u, #b. Responsible for the planning and direction of his unit's aerial operations against the enemy, #p has contributed immensely to increase his unit's effectiveness, as a result of his brilliant leadership, professional skill and detailed knowledge of modern air warfare. The singularly distinctive accomplishments of #p reflect great credit upon himself and the #s.
<b>
<b>
<r>
Moskva, #d  .