<c>
ROSSIYSKAYA FEDERATSIYA
<b>
*   *    ((*))    *   *
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT
of the Russian Federation
takes great pride in presenting
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
with a second
<b>
MEDAL "ZOLOTA ZVEZDA"
( #m )
<b>
<b>
<l>
#p, already a famed Hero of the Russian Federation, distinguished himself by extraordinary heroism at the risk of his life, in aerial action over #t, on #d. On that date, #p aggressively engaged the enemy with complete disregard for his personal safety, and enabled his unit, #u, to successfully complete the mission against an opposing force of overwhelming numerical superiority, with extreme prejudice for the enemy. This second award will testify that #p has much deserved the Peoples of Russia's gratitude.