<c>
ROSSIYSKAYA FEDERATSIYA
<b>
*   *    ((*))    *   *
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT
of the Russian Federation
takes pride in Conferring the
<b>
ORDEN ALEKSANDRA NEVSKOGO
( #m )
<b>
on
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
On #d, #p took a prominent part in aerial operations of major strategic importance over #t, and by his aggressive initiative, his inspiring leadership, and personal bravery in battle, enabled the outstanding success of his force against overwhelming odds. His composure and skilfulness in action, and his selfless devotion to duty, reflect great credit upon #p, and bring honour to his unit, #u.