<c>
ROSSIYSKAYA FEDERATSIYA
<b>
*   *    ((*))    *   *
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT
of the Russian Federation
has exceptionally
Approved and Ordered that the
<b>
ORDEN ALEKSANDRA NEVSKOGO
( #m )
<b>
shall be Conferred on
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
For exceptionally meritorious and distinguished service in a position of great responsibility as the deputy CO of the aviation regiment based at #b. In this important assignment, #p's ceaseless efforts, total dedication, and exceptional managerial abilities have immeasurably strengthened his unit's efficiency, resulting in 100 per cent effectiveness. Through his outstanding achievements, and dynamic leadership and initiative, #p has demonstrated the highest qualities of an #s field officer and rendered service of the greatest distinction to his country.