<c>
ROSSIYSKAYA FEDERATSIYA
<b>
*   *    ((*))    *   *
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT
of the Russian Federation
takes pride in Conferring the
<b>
ORDEN KUTUZOVA III Step.
( #m )
<b>
on
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
On #d, #p, a remarkable field officer in the #u, led combined aerial operations of critical strategic importance over #t, and by his professional skill, careful planning, and perfect knowledge of modern air warfare, ensured the decisive victory of his forces over a fierce opposition. The sound judgment, superior initiative, and dynamic leadership displayed by #p reflect great credit upon himself, and bring honour to the #u.