<c>
ROSSIYSKAYA FEDERATSIYA
<b>
*   *    ((*))    *   *
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT
of the Russian Federation
takes pride in presenting the
<b>
GEORGEVSKIY KREST II Step.
( #m )
<b>
to
<b>
#P
#u
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
For outstanding heroism in combat action. On #d, #p aggressively engaged an outnumbering hostile force over #t, with complete disregard for his personal safety, and successfully accomplished his assigned mission in the face of deadly fire, inflicting heavy damage upon the enemy. #p's repeated achievements reflect great credit upon himself and the #s.