<c>
ROSSIYSKAYA FEDERATSIYA
<b>
*   *    ((*))    *   *
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT
of the Russian Federation
takes pride in presenting the
<b>
MEDAL ORDENA
"ZA ZASLUGI PERED OTETSESTVOM"
II Stepeni s Mechami
( #m
to the Fatherland, with Swords )
<b>
to
<b>
#P,
presently serving within the
#u,
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
By continuing devotion, and gallantry, and spirit as a seasoned military pilot, #p has rendered the most distinguished service to his country, in close action against the enemies of Russia.
<b>
<b>
<r>
Moskva, #d  .