<c>
ROSSIYSKAYA FEDERATSIYA
<b>
*   *    ((*))    *   *
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT
of the Russian Federation
has exceptionally
Approved and Ordered that the
<b>
ORDEN "ZA ZASLUGI PERED
OTETSESTVOM" III Step.
( #m
to the Fatherland )
<b>
shall be Conferred on
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
#p displayed exceptionally distinguished performance of duty in wartime while serving as a remarkable leader within the #u. During the past months, he has many times fearlessly engaged enemy forces in spite of terrible odds, and his bravery, courage, and leadership directly contributed to his unit's ability to inflict decisive damage to the enemies of Russia - himself claiming an astounding score confirmedly exceeding by large forty jet aircraft shot down! Now a world-renowned ace pilot, #p has once more proved to be one of these great national heroes who make the pride of every Russian patriot.
<b>
<b>
<r>
Moskva, #d  .