<c>
ROSSIYSKAYA FEDERATSIYA
<b>
*   *    ((*))    *   *
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT
of the Russian Federation
takes pride in Conferring the
<b>
ORDEN "ZA ZASLUGI PERED
OTETSESTVOM" IV Step. s Mechami
( #m
to the Fatherland, with Swords )
<b>
on
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
In continuing aerial combat operations against the enemies of Russia, #p repeatedly displayed an outstanding mastery of aerial combat, proved conspicuous valor, and achieved national fame as an ace pilot, by taking part in the destruction of over twenty enemy air targets inflight. Fighting with a constant ardour in the most hazardous conditions, #p has many times proved to be one of these unswerving heroes through whom Eternal Russia shall stay alive.
<b>
<b>
<r>
Moskva, #d  .