<c>
<b>
* *  Voenno-Vozdushnye Sily Rossii  * *
<b>
<b>
<b>
<b>
By special order from
the Commander-in-Chief of the
#s,
<b>
#P
#u
<b>
has exceptionally been allowed
to proudly display the most coveted
<b>
Nagrudniy znak klassnoy kvalifikatsii
"VOENNIY LYOTCHIK-SNAYPER"
( Qualification badge "#m" )
<b>
<b>
<b>
<l>
Through his invaluable experience accumulated in real combat, his repeated outstanding achievements in battle, and his telling personal score as an ace pilot, #p has made much more than necessary to prove that he stands among the very top pilots of our #s, and thus that even while not fulfilling all of the regulation requirements, he is by large worthy bearing with pride this most coveted badge.
<b>
<b>
<r>
Moskva, #d,  .