<c>
MINISTERSTVO OBORONY
<b>
Rossiskoy Federatsii
<b>
<b>
<b>
<b>
The Minister of Defense
hereby certifies that
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
has been awarded the
<b>
MEDAL "ZA VOYNSKUYU DOBLEST"
I Stepeni
( #m )
<b>
<b>
<b>
<l>
For distinguishing himself by meritorious achievement while participating in sustained aerial flight in support of active military operations. During these flights, he displayed the highest order of air discipline and acted in accordance with the best traditions of the military service.
<b>
<b>
<r>
On #d,  .