<c>
Türkiye Cumhuriyeti
<b>
ORDER OF THE PRESIDENT
OF THE REPUBLIC OF TURKEY
Ankara
<b>
The President of the Republic,
on behalf of a grateful nation, 
hereby presents our nation's 
second-highest award for bravery, the:
<b>
#M
<b>
to
<b>
#P
#S
<b>
for service as set forth in the following
CITATION:
<b>
<l>
For conspicuous gallantry and skill, above and beyond the call of duty as a #a pilot, in action against enemy forces over #t, #d. #p aggressively engaged the enemy with great disregard for his own safety, against overwhelming odds. His actions and continuing exemplary service are in the highest traditions of the Turkish Air Force.