<c>
Türkiye Cumhuriyeti
<b>
ORDER OF THE CHIEF OF STAFF
OF THE TURKISH AIR FORCE
Ankara
<b>
The Chief of Staff of the Turkish Air Force 
hereby presents our nation's third-highest 
award for bravery, the:
<b>
#M
<b>
to
<b>
#P
#S
<b>
for service as set forth in the following
CITATION:
<b>
<l>
For conspicuous gallantry as a #a pilot, in action against enemy forces over #t, #d. #p engaged the enemy with great disregard for his own safety. His actions and example are in the highest tradition of the Turkish Air Force.