<c>
Türkiye Cumhuriyeti
<b>
ORDER OF THE CHIEF OF STAFF
OF THE TURKISH AIR FORCE
Ankara
<b>
The Chief of Staff 
of the Turkish Air Force 
hereby presents the:
<b>
#M
<b>
to
<b>
#P
#S
<b>
for service as set forth in the following
CITATION:
<b>
<l>
In recognition of the wounds sustained by #p in aerial combat over #t on #d. On this date, #p displayed great determination to complete his assigned mission in the face of heavy enemy fire, heedless of the wounds sustained by him, in the highest traditions of the Turkish Air Force.