<c>
<b>
<b>
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT OF UKRAINE
takes great pride in presenting
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
with a second
<b>
ORDEN "ZOLOTA ZIRKA"
( #m )
<b>
<b>
<l>
#p, already a famed Hero of Ukraine, distinguished himself by extraordinary heroism at the risk of his life, in aerial action over #t, on #d. On that date, #p aggressively engaged the enemy with complete disregard for his personal safety, and enabled his unit, #u, to successfully complete the mission against an opposing force of overwhelming numerical superiority, with extreme prejudice for the enemy. This second award will testify that #p has much deserved the Ukrainian Nation's gratitude.