<c>
<b>
<b>
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT OF UKRAINE
takes pride in Conferring the
<b>
ORDEN "ZA MUZHNIST" II Stup.
( #m )
<b>
on
<b>
#P
#u
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
#p distinguished himself by outstanding heroism in combat action over #t, on #d. On that date, he aggressively engaged an outnumbering hostile force, with complete disregard for his personal safety, and successfully accomplished his assigned mission in the face of deadly fire, inflicting heavy damage upon the enemy. #p's repeated achievements reflect great credit upon himself and the #s.