<c>
<b>
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT OF UKRAINE
<b>
has exceptionally
Approved and Ordered that the
<b>
ORDEN "ZA MUZHNIST" I Stup.
( #m )
<b>
shall be Conferred on
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
On #d, #p, renowned already as a Hero of Ukraine, fearlessly engaged a hostile force over #t, facing extremely determined opposition and overwhelming odds, yet could inflict crippling damage upon the enemy. These neckband and breast star will testify to Ukraine's eternal respect for the great military feats achieved by #p.