<c>
<b>
<b>
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT OF UKRAINE
takes pride in Conferring the
<b>
ORDEN "ZA MUZHNIST" III Stup.
( #m )
<b>
on
<b>
#P
#u
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
On #d, #p proved exemplary valor while engaged in uneven aerial combat over #t. On that occasion, he displayed superior airmanship skills and abnegation to successfully complete his assigned mission, inflicting heavy damage upon the enemy. #p's exemplary conduct and courage reflect great credit upon himself and the #s.