<c>
<b>
<b>
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT OF UKRAINE
takes great pride in Conferring on
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
the Title of
<b>
HEROY UKRAYINY
( #m )
<b>
jointly with the Order of the Gold Star.
<b>
<b>
<l>
#p distinguished himself by conspicuous gallantry and intrepidity at the risk of his life, in action against hostile forces over #t, on #d. On that date, #p fearlessly engaged the enemy against overwhelming odds, and by his courage and leadership, directly contributed to his unit, #u, achieving outstanding mission success. His devotion to duty and unquestionable patriotic faith reflect great credit upon himself, his glorious unit, and the whole #s.