<c>
<b>
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT OF UKRAINE
<b>
has exceptionally
Approved and Ordered that the
<b>
ORDEN BOHDANA KHMELNYTSKOHO I Stup.
( Order of #m )
<b>
shall be Conferred on
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
In charge of the air component during combined operations of critical strategic importance over #t, on #d, #p managed to secure the complete victory of the forces under his command against overwhelming odds, through his calculated boldness, decisiveness, and complete control over modern air warfare. An exceptionally inspired planner and a natural born leader, #p brings great honour to the whole #s.