<c>
<b>
<b>
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT OF UKRAINE
takes pride in Conferring the
<b>
ORDEN "ZA ZASLUHY"
II Stupenya z Mechamy
( #m with Swords )
<b>
on
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
In continuing aerial combat operations in the defense of Ukraine, #p repeatedly displayed an outstanding mastery of aerial combat, proved conspicuous valor, and achieved national fame as an ace pilot, by taking part in the destruction of over twenty enemy air targets inflight. Fighting with a constant ardour in the most hazardous conditions, #p has many times proved to be one of these unswerving heroes through whom the Ukrainian Nation shall stay alive.
<b>
<b>
<r>
Kyiv, #d  .