<c>
<b>
<b>
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT OF UKRAINE
takes pride in Conferring the
<b>
ORDEN DANYLA HALYTSKOHO
z Mechamy
( #m, with Swords )
<b>
on
<b>
#P,
presently serving within the
#u,
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
By continuing devotion, and gallantry, and spirit as a seasoned military pilot, #p has rendered the most distinguished service to his country, in close action against the enemies of Ukraine.
<b>
<b>
<r>
Kyiv, #d  .