<c>
<b>
<b>
<b>
<b>
THE PRESIDENT OF UKRAINE
takes pride in Conferring the
<b>
ORDEN "ZA ZASLUHY"
III Stupenya z Mechamy
( #m with Swords )
<b>
on
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
<b>
<l>
As an excellent officer, and an ace pilot of note, #p has displayed incomparable and daring airmanship to successfully complete his assigned missions, himself engaging the enemy in many victorious contests. Through his gallantry and his devotion to duty, he demonstrates the highest values of an Ukrainian patriot, and renders service of the greatest distinction to the Republic.
<b>
<b>
<r>
Kyiv, #d  .