<c>
Povitriani Syly  Ukrayiny
_ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _ _
<b>
<b>
<b>
<b>
By special order from
the Commander-in-Chief of the
#s,
<b>
#P
#u
<b>
has exceptionally been allowed
to display the
<b>
Nahrudniy znak klasniy fakhivets
"VIYSKOVIY LOTCHYK-SNAYPER"
( Qualification badge "#m" )
<b>
<b>
<b>
<l>
Through his invaluable experience accumulated in real combat, his repeated outstanding achievements in battle, and his telling personal score as an ace pilot, #p has made much more than necessary to prove that he stands among the very top pilots of our #s, and thus that even while not fulfilling all of the regulation requirements, he is by large worthy bearing with pride this most coveted badge.
<b>
<b>
<r>
Kyiv, #d,  .