<r>
<b>
#d
<c>
<b>
<b>
<b>
This is to certify that
the Chief of the General Staff
of the Armed Forces of Ukraine
has expressed congratulations to
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
"ZA DOBLESNU VIYSKOVU
SLUZHBU BATKIVSHCHYNI"
( #m
to the Fatherland )
<b>
<b>
<l>
For exceptionally meritorious and distinguished service in a position of great responsibility as the deputy CO of the aviation brigade based at #b. In this important assignment, #p's ceaseless efforts, total dedication, and exceptional managerial abilities have immeasurably strengthened his unit's efficiency, resulting in 100 per cent effectiveness. Through his outstanding achievements, and dynamic leadership and initiative, #p has demonstrated the highest qualities of an #s field officer and rendered service of the greatest distinction to his country.