<r>
<b>
#d
<c>
<b>
<b>
<b>
This is to certify that
the Chief of the General Staff
of the Armed Forces of Ukraine
has expressed his appreciation to
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
"ZA DOSYAHNENNYA U VIYSKOVIY SLUZHBI"
I Stupenya
( #m )
<b>
<b>
<l>
For exceptionally meritorious and distinguished service as a deputy squadron CO within the #u, #b. Responsible for the planning and direction of his unit's aerial operations against the enemy, #p has contributed immensely to increase his unit's effectiveness, as a result of his brilliant leadership, professional skill and detailed knowledge of modern air warfare. The singularly distinctive accomplishments of #p reflect great credit upon himself and the #s.