<c>
MINISTERSTVO OBORONY UKRAYINY
<b>
<b>
<b>
The Minister of Defense
hereby certifies that
<b>
#P
#s
<b>
has been awarded the
<b>
Vijnaka Ministerstva Oborony Ukrayiny
"DOBLEST I CHEST"
( #m )
<b>
<b>
<l>
#p distinguished himself by exceptionally meritorious conduct in the performance of outstanding services to Ukraine, while serving as a #a squadron leader, #u. During this assignment, the leadership, exemplary foresight, and personal courage consistently demonstrated by #p were instrumental factors in his unit's ability to achieve the most demanding missions. By his unquestionable devotion to duty, #p has rendered invaluable and distinguished service and contributed greatly to the continued success of the current aerial campaign, thereby upholding the highest traditions of the #s.
<b>
<b>
<r>
On #d,  .